<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>StrangeSeeings</title>
    <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing" />
    <updated>2021-02-14T13:51:27+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Graham</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Blog</title>
        <author>
            <name>Graham</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/blog.html"/>
        <id>https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/blog.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-14T13:51:27+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>History of UFOs</title>
        <author>
            <name>Graham</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/history-of-ufos.html"/>
        <id>https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/history-of-ufos.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-14T13:48:31+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     It may be that the history of UFOs pre-dates our own history. Science currently says that the Universe is 13.8 billion years old and the Earth is 4.6 billion years old. We now know also that planets are quite common around stars. So given&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <p>It may be that the history of UFOs pre-dates our own history. Science currently says that the Universe is 13.8 billion years old and the Earth is 4.6 billion years old. We now know also that planets are quite common around stars. So given the vastness of the Universe, there may potentially be many millions of worlds which were in existence for billions of years before earth formed.</p><br><p>We also now know that some planets are in the inhabitable zone which could support life – not too near to their star (unlike Mercury and Venus) and not too far away (unlike Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, Neptune and Pluto). As evolution on Earth shows us that natural selection produces generations of ever more intelligent animals, we can assume that this evolutionary dynamic may well operate on other worlds too. Hence it is quite possible that there are intelligent beings on other worlds and that they evolved billions of years before Earth was created.</p><br><p>Human science and technology has advanced steadily in the 200,000 years since Homo Sapiens first appeared on Earth. Imagine how far advanced would be the technology of a civilisation which began on a faraway world several billion years before earth was formed. If it is possible to traverse the great distances in space, they may well have found it several billion years ago.</p><br><p>Therefore if aliens exist it is quite possible that they know more about us than we do.</p><br><br><h2>Ancient evidence of UFOs and aliens</h2><br><p>NASA, the American National Aeronautics and Space Administration, is an organisation which rarely talks about UFOs and aliens. Astonishingly there is a PDF on their site, written in 2007 by a former member of staff, R. Stothers, which describes ancient UFO sightings. I have attached the full PDF here. Broadly the text concludes that UFOs fascinated the ancients and still fascinate us today, for many of the same reasons.</p><br><br><h2>Prehistoric Art</h2><br><img loading="lazy" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/dtebvnzsp/image/upload/v1537903623/8af63f69891794531116bc858c35ae22.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Prehistoric cave painting of alien?"><br><br><p>This extraordinary image is a Wandjina spirit painting Petroglyph from Kimberly, Australia. It has been dated at approximately 3000 BC. The figures painted closely resemble the descriptions of entities reported by people who claim to have glimpsed strange creatures near landed UFOs, or who claim to have been abducted into UFOs. Of course the resemblance could be a coincidence, but it is a striking coincidence that aboriginal Australian people, who at that time had never seen Europeans with lighter skin, should paint these light-skinned figures with large dark eyes.</p><br><img loading="lazy" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/dtebvnzsp/image/upload/v1537903624/1350178.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Prehistoric painting of alien?"><br><br><br><p>This image was painted in China 47,000 years ago.</p><br><br><img loading="lazy" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/dtebvnzsp/image/upload/v1537903623/7f6b2a4c65d8386dd3b66142b0f4659b.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Prehistoric painting of alien?"><br><br><p>Finally here is another prehistoric cave painting. I am still researching the age and location of this one. Notice the strange disc shaped and cigar shaped objects to the right of the figure, which resembles a humanoid in a hazard or space suit.</p><br><br><h2>Ancient Art and Writings</h2><br><p></p>Ancient civilisations developed not just art, but also writing, and this enabled may recordings of phenomena which would today be called UFOs.<p></p><br><br><h2>Josephus</h2><br><p>The historian Josephus in approximately 65 A.D. wrote of a sighting over the ancient region of Judea. The sighting described ‘miraculous’ chariots in the sky and what seemed to him to be ‘battalions’ in the sky. Of course at this time Josephus and his contemporaries would have had no framework to be able to describe what they saw. It would be nearly 2,000 years before the first aircraft, balloon or (human) spacecraft.</p><br><br><p>Often ancient accounts speak of ‘glowing shields’ which is pretty much what many UFOs look like, since many ancient shields were round and flat with a protruding dome in the middle.</p><br><br><h2>Medieval and Renaissance Art and Writings</h2><br><img loading="lazy" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/dtebvnzsp/image/upload/v1537903623/862d588af8a46b78ce00ca57ff4ca82e-2.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="UFO in renaissance painting"><br><br><p>“The Madonna with Saint Giovannino”, above, is a painting by the 15th century artist Domenico. It shows what appears to be a UFO on the sky behind Mary.</p><br><br><img loading="lazy" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/dtebvnzsp/image/upload/v1537903624/transmiss05.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="UFO in medieval painting"><br><br><p>This fresco painted in 1350 depicts “The Crucifixion” in the Visoki Decani Monestary in Kosovo, Serbia. There are two UFO-like objects, one either side of Jesus.</p><br><br><p>If we are being visited, there is no reason to assume, given the great age of the universe, that the visits began recently. They may have begun thousands, tens of thousands, hundreds of thousands or millions of years ago.</p>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Best Evidence</title>
        <author>
            <name>Graham</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/best-evidence.html"/>
        <id>https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/best-evidence.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-14T13:46:34+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Here is our growing list of the best evidence about UFOs. The famous incident in 1947 which helped to start the modern phenomenon. Read more here. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <p>Here is our growing list of the best evidence about UFOs.</p><p><br></p><h2>The Roswell Incident</h2><p><br></p><p>The famous incident in 1947 which helped to start the modern phenomenon. Read more <a href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/the-roswell-incident-1947.html" class="">here</a>.</p>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About</title>
        <author>
            <name>Graham</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/about.html"/>
        <id>https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/about.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-14T13:47:28+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     I have been interested in UFOs since the 1970s and have quietly watched developments in the field of what has become known as ‘Ufology’. ‘Ufology’ has a scientific sound to it and many UFO researchers yearn for scientific respectability. I have doubts about the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    <p>I have been interested in UFOs since the 1970s and have quietly watched developments in the field of what has become known as ‘Ufology’.<br><br></p><p>‘Ufology’ has a scientific sound to it and many UFO researchers yearn for scientific respectability. I have doubts about the term. Much of the study of UFOs is anything but scientific, and indeed is packed with disinformation from fraudsters, delusional individuals, attention seekers and possibly government disinformation too. On UFOs, often it seems that those who know do not tell, and those who do not know tell us a lot. Selectivity and rigorousness are crucial attributes of serious UFO researchers but too many of them have little of these.<br><br></p><p>Personally I have seen two UFOs, meaning unidentified objects in the sky. One was while on holiday in Cuzco, Peru. It was a bright strangely shaped object that hung motionless for a short while; when I looked again it was gone. I cannot draw any conclusions about what it was. My other sighting was a brief glimpse of an apparently light grey disc which flew overhead in northern England where I live. The sighting lasted for about three seconds on a bright sunny day with little cloud. The sun was in a different part of the sky, and the only other possibility was that I was looking at a helicopter but it made no sound and seemed to disappear in a clear blue windless sky. Fascinating, but neither of these sightings convince me let alone anyone else.<br><br></p><p>The great writer Arthur C Clarke said that anyone who has not seen a few UFOs is not very observant – he had seen several but did not ‘believe’ in UFOs. The mind can play tricks.<br><br></p><p>However having digested a lot of evidence on the subject of UFOs I am of the opinion that there is something to the subject and that there are machines and beings visiting Earth which are not from Earth, or are not from this dimension of Earth, or are not from our time on Earth.<br><br></p><p>In this blog I attempt to guide you through the most credible and cohesive information about UFOs and the beings who make them.<br><br></p><p>Enjoy.</p>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A rational look at UFOs</title>
        <author>
            <name>Graham</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/a-rational-look-at-ufos.html"/>
        <id>https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/a-rational-look-at-ufos.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-14T13:27:16+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     This site is intended as a rational person’s guide to the fascinating phenomena of UFOs and aliens. ‘UFOs’ are defined here as any unidentified flying object or unexplained aerial phenomena. ‘Aliens’ are the presumed manufacturers and pilots of these objects or creators of the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p id="this-site-is-intended-as-a-rational-persons-guide-to-the-fascinating-phenomena-of-ufos-and-aliensbr----------------ufos-are-defined-here-as-any-unidentified-flying-object-or-unexplained-aerial-phenomena-aliens-are-the-presumed-manufacturers-and-pilots-of-these-objects-or-creators-of-the-phenomenabr----------------perhaps-not-all-ufos-are-piloted-by-aliens-but-it-may-be-that-at-least-some-are-an-alien-could-conceivably-come-from-another-part-of-the-universe-another-dimension-or-another-time-increasingly-it-seems-that-some-ufos-may-actually-only-be-unidentified-to-the-general-public-but-positively-identified-to-the-military-organisations-which-secretly-created-thembr----------------it-should-always-be-remembered-that-approximately-98-of-all-unidentified-and-aerial-phenomena-can-be-rationally-explained-the-2-which-remain-unexplained-are-what-we-are-interested-inbr------------br">
    This site is intended as a rational person’s guide to the fascinating phenomena of UFOs and aliens.<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    ‘UFOs’ are defined here as any unidentified flying object or unexplained aerial phenomena. ‘Aliens’ are the presumed manufacturers and pilots of these objects or creators of the phenomena.<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    Perhaps not all ‘UFOs’ are piloted by aliens, but it may be that at least some are. An ‘alien’ could conceivably come from another part of the universe, another dimension or another time.&nbsp;<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    Increasingly it seems that some ‘UFOs’ may actually only be unidentified to the general public but positively identified to the military organisations which secretly created them.<br>It should always be remembered that approximately 98% of all unidentified and aerial phenomena can be rationally explained. The 2% which remain unexplained are what we are interested in.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Roswell Incident 1947</title>
        <author>
            <name>Graham</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/the-roswell-incident-1947.html"/>
        <id>https://grafrajohn.github.io/StrangeSeeing/the-roswell-incident-1947.html</id>

        <updated>2021-02-14T13:08:43+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     The fabled Roswell Incident took place in July 1947 and is either the greatest myth of modern times or the greatest deception of all time. It is a great story, has become a great commercial vehicle, an entertainment vehicle and it is even claimed&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    The fabled Roswell Incident took place in July 1947 and is either the greatest myth of modern times or the greatest deception of all time. It is a great story, has become a great commercial vehicle, an entertainment vehicle and it is even claimed to have provided us with the core technologies of the late twentieth century! It seems that either there were several crashes at around the same time or the memories of some of the witnesses have become confused with slightly different sites, dates and circumstances being given.<br><br>What is odd about the Roswell incident is that the local newspaper, which was staffed by typically savvy and enquiring journalists, printed a story which stated that a UFO had crashed. Here it is:
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/etl4ogzsdjc37pueauft.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/etl4ogzsdjc37pueauft-xs.jpg 300w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/etl4ogzsdjc37pueauft-sm.jpg 480w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/etl4ogzsdjc37pueauft-md.jpg 768w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/etl4ogzsdjc37pueauft-lg.jpg 1024w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/etl4ogzsdjc37pueauft-xl.jpg 1360w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/etl4ogzsdjc37pueauft-2xl.jpg 1600w"  height="432" width="652" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    Other newspapers printed further stories:
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/san_mateo_times_jul_8_1947-276171230_std.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/san_mateo_times_jul_8_1947-276171230_std-xs.jpg 300w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/san_mateo_times_jul_8_1947-276171230_std-sm.jpg 480w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/san_mateo_times_jul_8_1947-276171230_std-md.jpg 768w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/san_mateo_times_jul_8_1947-276171230_std-lg.jpg 1024w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/san_mateo_times_jul_8_1947-276171230_std-xl.jpg 1360w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/san_mateo_times_jul_8_1947-276171230_std-2xl.jpg 1600w"  height="439" width="487" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    One has to remember that this was in an age when there was no previous history of UFOs, at least as far as most citizens knew. So it may be that the local air base decided they would tell the world about it. And it may also be that in Washington, powerful people had very different ideas.<br><br>Soon the staff at the Roswell air base were forced to tell the world that the ‘flying disk’ was really a weather ballon. Something of oversight for very highly security cleared aviators. This aspect of the story is itself unbelievable – how would the men at Roswell, the only crews cleared to carry and drop the atom bomb, mistake an everyday weather ballon for a flying disk. Many people do not believe it.
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/o-roswell-ufo-facebook-768x837.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/o-roswell-ufo-facebook-768x837-xs.jpg 300w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/o-roswell-ufo-facebook-768x837-sm.jpg 480w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/o-roswell-ufo-facebook-768x837-md.jpg 768w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/o-roswell-ufo-facebook-768x837-lg.jpg 1024w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/o-roswell-ufo-facebook-768x837-xl.jpg 1360w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/o-roswell-ufo-facebook-768x837-2xl.jpg 1600w"  height="837" width="768" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    Here Major Jesse Marcel is made to display the ‘weather ballon’ to the press. Around the time this happened, the local area was teeming with armed forces personnel who, according to local witnesses, were threatening violence and even death to anyone who talked about the crash incident. Hardly surprisingly, the ether soon fell silent on the subject of the crashed object. To this day the American military deny that anything crashed at Roswell, even when their elected President asks about it.<br><br>Several witnesses have drawn both the crashed craft and its crew, and here are their impressions. This photograph is actually of a model kit of the craft, so popular has the Roswell story become around the world.
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/bairnufod.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/bairnufod-xs.jpg 300w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/bairnufod-sm.jpg 480w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/bairnufod-md.jpg 768w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/bairnufod-lg.jpg 1024w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/bairnufod-xl.jpg 1360w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/bairnufod-2xl.jpg 1600w"  height="338" width="450" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    The craft had several inhabitants. Unsurprisingly it seems they were in a bad way; witnesses say some were dead and at least one was alive at the time the downed craft was discovered.<br><br>The crew were described as small humanoid creatures and the sketch below is believed to be by a first hand witness.
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/nursesketch1.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/nursesketch1-xs.jpg 300w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/nursesketch1-sm.jpg 480w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/nursesketch1-md.jpg 768w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/nursesketch1-lg.jpg 1024w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/nursesketch1-xl.jpg 1360w ,file:///Users/grahamjohnson/Documents/Publii/sites/strangeseeings/input/media/posts/temp/responsive/nursesketch1-2xl.jpg 1600w"  height="432" width="350" alt="" />
      
    </figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
